<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
  <title>endromeda - rss</title>
  <description>endromeda articles, on rss!</description>
  <link>https://endromeda.neocities.org/</link>
  <lastBuildDate>
    Sat, 22 May 2021
  </lastBuildDate>
  <ttl>20000</ttl>
  <item>
    <title>Minor Updates</title>
    <description>
      i haddn't done that much updates to this site as i did before. main reason being i don't know what to add to this website, but i added some things to endromeda.
	  but, i added some minor updates. such updates are making the posts page organized by month, less ugly article dates, and a viewer for images
    </description>
    <link>https://endromeda.neocities.org/</link>
    <pubDate>
      Wen, 22 July 2021 00:00:00 PST
    </pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Ubuntu is horrible</title>
    <description>
      Ubuntu is a Linux Distro that has a terrible theme, so much bloat, and a resource hog to systems. Ubuntu is a fine starter distro but there is much better Linux distros that are ALSO easy to use.
    </description>
    <link>https://endromeda.neocities.org/news/2021/7-21-ubuntu.html</link>
    <pubDate>
      Wen, 21 July 2021 15:17:00 PST
    </pubDate>
  </item>
    <item>
    <title>Windows XP is Overrated</title>
    <description>
Windows XP is one of the most ugliest and the
most overrated operating system known to man.
And people who weren't even born when XP was
released says that it's the "best OS" ever.
    </description>
    <link>https://endromeda.neocities.org/news/2021/7-13-winxp_sucks.html</link>
    <pubDate>
      Wen, 13 July 2021 15:17:00 PST
    </pubDate>
  </item>
    <item>
    <title>Endromeda on old browsers</title>
    <description>
My friend wants me to post about this so i'm
going to do it :troll:. He made a proxy that
loads this website without CSS (and in HTTP).
    </description>
    <link>https://endromeda.neocities.org/news/2021/7-12-endromeda-proxy.html</link>
    <pubDate>
      Wen, 12 July 2021 15:17:00 PST
    </pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Articles are now posts</title>
    <description>
      The articles section is now renamed to Posts. This allows me to make blog-like posts along side articles on endromeda.
    </description>
    <link>https://endromeda.neocities.org/news/2021/7-12-first_post.html</link>
    <pubDate>
      Mon, 12 July 2021 09:58:00 PST
    </pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>A First Look at Windows 11</title>
    <description>
      We're going to take a first look on Microsoft's recently leaked Operating System, Windows 11. Which, I took a test drive on a VM. It sucks, ALOT.
    </description>
    <link>https://endromeda.neocities.org/2021/6-16-win11.html</link>
    <pubDate>
      Wen, 16 June 2021 12:53:00 PST
    </pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>endromeda BETA</title>
    <description>
      i have a beta website, where i try out new things and see if they should be on the main website, the beta page is at /beta/.
    </description>
    <link>https://endromeda.neocities.org/beta</link>
    <pubDate>
      Sat, 12 June 2021 14:04:00 PST
    </pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>DeviantART Sucks</title>
    <description>
      The DeviantART redesign is one of the worst redesigns i've ever seen, Even worse than YouTube Polymer, it's a buggy, slow, confusing mess of a redesign.
    </description>
    <link>https://endromeda.neocities.org/news/2021/5-26-deviantart.html</link>
    <pubDate>
      Wed, 26 May 2021 07:01:00 PST
    </pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Article Pages Change</title>
    <description>
      All existing article pages has been moved and renamed, to be more organized once more articles come.
    </description>
    <link>https://endromeda.neocities.org/</link>
    <pubDate>
      Sat, 22 May 2021 06:19:00 PST
    </pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Gnome 3 and KDE 4/5 Sucks</title>
    <description>
      Gnome 3 and KDE Plasma is trash, every setup I see with one of them looks so ugly and blinds my eyes. Gnome and KDE had lost their way on making a actual good Desktop enviornment.
    </description>
    <link>https://endromeda.neocities.org/news/2021/5-8-kdegnome.html</link>
    <pubDate>
      Sat, 8 May 2021
    </pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The OIC is a drama landfill</title>
    <description>
      The OIC (Old Internet Community) is an kindergarden playground and 5 year old kids fighting around, but it's through harrassment and doxxing. OIC is a hellhole powered by toxicity.
    </description>
    <link>https://endromeda.neocities.org/news/2021/5-4-oic.html</link>
    <pubDate>
      Tue, 4 May 2021
    </pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Windows 10 is a dumpster</title>
    <description>
      Windows 10 is a absolute dumpster in fire. It's a absolute resource hogger, it's spyware and looks terrible, There is some ways to make Windows 10 a bit more tollerable.
    </description>
    <link>https://endromeda.neocities.org/news/2021/5-3-win10.html</link>
    <pubDate>
      Mon, 3 May 2021
    </pubDate>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Why Firefox Proton is SHIT</title>
    <description>
     Somewhere in Febuary 2021, Firefox has put a new Proton redesign in the nightly builds of Firefox. In this article, i'm going to be ranting on why the Firefox Proton redesign is absolute SHIT.
    </description>
    <link>https://endromeda.neocities.org/news/2021/5-3-firefox-proton.html</link>
    <pubDate>
      Mon, 3 May 2021
    </pubDate>
  </item>
</channel>
</rss>
